[
  {
    "id": "405",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A subnet maps to how many AZs?",
      "answers": [
        "one",
        "two",
        "many"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["one"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "406",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you terminate an EC2 instance, its attached root EBS volume will be deleted by default?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "407",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If you don't want the root EBS volume to be deleted when you terminate its EC2 instance, you can do which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "uncheck the Delete on Termination checkbox in the console",
        "use the cli to change the delete on termination status for the volume",
        "you can't make the root volume continue to exist if you terminate its EC2 instance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["uncheck the Delete on Termination checkbox in the console"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "408",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 status check verifies that your EC2 instance is reachable?",
      "answers": [
        "System Status Check",
        "Instance Status Check"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["System Status Check"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "409",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 status check verifies that you can get network packets to your instance?",
      "answers": [
        "System Status Check",
        "Instance Status Check"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["System Status Check"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "410",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If this status check fails there may be an issue with the infrastructure of the EC2 instance, such as power, OS, or networking?",
      "answers": [
        "System Status Check",
        "Instance Status Check"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["System Status Check"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "411",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 status check verifies that your instance is accepting traffic?",
      "answers": [
        "System Status Check",
        "Instance Status Check"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Instance Status Check"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "412",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Basic monitoring of an EC2 instance occurs every _____ minutes?",
      "answers": [
        "one",
        "five",
        "ten"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["five"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "413",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Detailed monitoring of an EC2 instance occurs every _____ minutes, and costs extra?",
      "answers": [
        "one",
        "five",
        "ten"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["one"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "414",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EC2 termination protection is _________ by default?",
      "answers": [
        "turned off",
        "turned on",
        "undefined"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["turned off"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "415",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You must do what to get termination protection for your EC2 instance?",
      "answers": [
        "explicitly turn it on for that instance",
        "accept the defaults when creating the instance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["explicitly turn it on for that instance"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "416",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "On an EBS-backed EC2 instance, the default action to take when the EC2 instance is terminated is what?",
      "answers": [
        "the EBS root volume is deleted when the EC2 instance is terminated",
        "the EBS root volume remains active when the EC2 instance is terminated",
        "the EBS root volume is inactive but still exists when the EC2 instance is terminated"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the EBS root volume is deleted when the EC2 instance is terminated"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "417",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EBS root volumes of the AMIs created by AWS (or the DEFAULT AMIs) _______?",
      "answers": [
        "cannot be encrypted",
        "can be encrypted"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["cannot be encrypted"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "418",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can use a third party tool (such as bit locker) to encrypt an AWS created AMI?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "419",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "You can create your own AMI copy of the AWS default AMI and encrypt the root EBS volume using which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS console",
        "AWS API",
        "you can't encrypt the root EBS volume when creating your own AMI copy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS console", "AWS API"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "420",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Additional EBS volumes added to your EC2 instance can be encrypted?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "421",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A security group is what?",
      "answers": [
        "virtual firewall controlling traffic to your instances",
        "a physical firewall controlling traffic to your instances",
        "an IAM security role",
        "an IAM security group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["virtual firewall controlling traffic to your instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "422",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An EC2 instance can have how many security groups?",
      "answers": [
        "one",
        "two",
        "multiple"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["multiple"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "423",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Any change applied to a security group is applied when?",
      "answers": [
        "immediately",
        "after the time to live (TTL) expires",
        "when the security groups for you instance are refreshed",
        "within several minutes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["immediately"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "424",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Security groups are ______?",
      "answers": [
        "stateful",
        "stateless",
        "without state",
        "of indeterminate state"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["stateful"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "425",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Since security groups are stateful, any traffic allowed in is __________?",
      "answers": [
        "allowed back out",
        "only allowed back out if an outbound rule is defined for that type of traffic"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["allowed back out"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "426",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you create an inbound security group rule a corresponding outbound rule is also added so that type of traffic is allowed back out again?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "427",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With security groups _________?",
      "answers": [
        "all traffic is denied by default",
        "all traffic is allowed by default",
        "there is no default defined"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["all traffic is denied by default"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "428",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "How do you allow traffic for a specific type of traffic using a security group?",
      "answers": [
        "you add a rule for that type of traffic on a specific port using a specific CIDR",
        "you define an IAM role and associate it with the security group",
        "you define an IAM policy and associate it with the security group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["you add a rule for that type of traffic on a specific port using a specific CIDR"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "429",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With security groups all outbound traffic is ________ by default?",
      "answers": [
        "allowed",
        "denied",
        "undefined"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["allowed"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "430",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can have how many EC2 instances within a security group?",
      "answers": [
        "one",
        "two",
        "multiple"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["multiple"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "431",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which do you use to block specific IP addresses access to your EC2 instance?",
      "answers": [
        "Security Group",
        "Network Access Control List",
        "IAM Role",
        "IAM Policy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Network Access Control List"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "432",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You cannot block specific IP addresses using security groups?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "433",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Using security groups you can specify which types of rules?",
      "answers": [
        "allow rules",
        "deny rules"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["allow rules"]
    }
  }
]
